研究。
啊！
各位早晨，蘇貞。
去早日完成立法。
維護國家安全條例草案。
去召開特別立法會會議。
正如行政長官多番表示。
就條例草案進行首讀同埋二讀。
政府同埋立法會都必須盡一切嘅努力。
我哋應合力，盡快堵塞國家安全嘅缺口。
喺剛才嘅立法會會議上咧，已經進行咗首讀同埋二讀。
昨日我係收到行政長官嘅來信，去建議盡快。
我亦認同相關嘅立法工作係有必要性同埋急切性。
法案委員會亦都係緊接喺今日下午咧，就條例草案咧係展開工作。
同基本法第二十三條相關事嘅小組委員會咧，而家已經變身成為。
事實上，《基本法》第二十三條立法係整個香港特區嘅憲制責任。
我相信。
早一日完成立法。
我係按照已是規則。
因此，作為立法會主席。
亦都接獲咗好多正面嘅意見。
維護國家安全立法係特區嘅憲制責任。
國家安全就會早日得到有效嘅維護。
亦向政府提出咗好多具體同埋建設性嘅意見。
細心去參詳議員嘅意見，去完善個法例。
依個既係主權國家嘅固有權利，亦都係國際嘅慣例。
我留意到喺諮詢期間，唔同嘅界別都係積極反映意見。
政府當局會繼續秉承秉持廣攬兼聽嘅精神。
諮詢嘅結果係顯示，就第二十三條立法係獲得高達九十八點六嘅百分比嘅支持。
政府喺今日立法會諮詢文件亦都提到，每個國家都會制定維護國家安全嘅法律。
議員亦都係之前嘅小組委員會同埋事務委員會聯席會議上咧，係充分如實反映市民嘅意見。
第十四一同埋二條例嘅規定，喺今日召開咗立法會會議，以盡快履行《基本法》第二十三條立法嘅重要建制責任。
我哋都有信心。
喺個重要嘅時刻。
我 also fully agree that.
亦係責任重大。
我用英文講幾句啦。
過去二十七年都未能完成。
改善民生，令一國兩制行穩致遠。
There is a genuine and urgent need for the legislation.
為國家、為香港穩定同埋發展努力。
能肩負呢個歷史嘅任務咧，係我哋第七屆立法會係感到光榮嘅。
喺完成制定有效維護國家安全法例之後咧，就能夠全力聚焦發展經濟。
both the government and Legco must make every effort to complete the legislation process as soon as possible.
全體議員一定係上下一心，全力以赴審慎審議法案條文，以履行我哋嘅憲制職能。
to legislate for Article Twenty-Three of Basic Law is the constitutional duty of the entire Hong Kong SAR.
在立法會會議剛剛，《 safeguarding national security》法案，被引入到議會進行第一次和第二次閲讀。
The sub committee to study matters relating to Basic Law Article 23 legislation has been turned into Bills Committee and will commence scrutiny of the bill immediately this afternoon.
and we have.
historic mission.
at this critical juncture.
fail to do so in the past 27 years.
and enact laws to safeguard national security.
Meanwhile, legislative members also reflect the views of the people.
as mentioned in the government consultation document, each country
It is the inherent right of the sovereign state, and the international practice.
The Seventh Legislative Council is honoured to be able to shoulder this historical.
with a view to contributing to the stability and development of the country and Hong Kong.
We would spare no effort and work together to plug the national security loophole as soon as possible.
enactment of legislation to safeguard national security is the constitutional duty of the Hong Kong SAR.
truthfully and gave specific and constructive advice to the government during the meetings of the subcommittees and joint panel.
I believe that the government will continue to listen extensively and study carefully members' views to enhance the legislation.
我 have note that ninety eight point six per cent of the views received during the consultation period support the legislative exercise and gave positive comments.
As the president of LECO, I call a meeting of the council today in accordance with sections 14, bracket one and bracket two of the rules of procedures to fulfil our constitutional duty.
四折。
軍事。
就這兩個人。
唔會繼續加。
You tell me.
大家有咩問題？
electrical for
resumption of second reading and the third reading.
Why are we rushing? We have you know in.
and ensure the steadfast and successful implementation of one country, two system.
two weeks, three weeks， they enact 15 to 20 laws. So why can't Hong Kong do it in a speedy manner?
The bill is necessary to safeguard the national security. We should enact it. If you look at other countries, they enact it in within a day.
Finish scrutiny, it went to you go to the House Committee for report, and then we'll then schedule when you'll come back to the.
I think right now the first reading and second reading had just been.
我有每有
Through is up to the bills committee to do the work, and I'm sure you know the bills committee will do everything possible to speed up the process. But I think with the legislature, everything is you know we have set process, and I think.
去加快嗰個立法。
is workable.
嗯。
好，大家嚟，唔該。
一日噉，但現時係冇死線，亦都冇一個時間表。
緊嘢啊，都留夜翻嚟嘅。咁呢個係佢嘅責任啊，亦都我諗係佢哋嘅榮幸。噉我諗你問個別議員點解佢會？
嗱，而家我哋已經進入一個立法程序。頭先咧就已經係首讀同埋二讀，咁跟住咧就因為我哋已經係。
翻到嚟去做啦，噉樣雖然琴日嘅通知係好急，但係誒大家都可以講到收到我通知，坐飛機喺北京都翻到嚟啊！嗯，冇錯。
開嗰個誒誒小組嗰陣時咧，已經講明咧，一去到首讀二讀咧，就會轉為一個泛愛委員會。咁泛愛委員會主席誒廖長江議員咧，就會同立法誒同呢個呢個泛愛委員會咧，會盡一切努力去完成呢個工作。立法。
法會嘅工作都係一步一步嘅，咁一定係要法案委會完成咗之後去內會彙報，咁然後至可以翻翻嚟大會。噉我哋係靜候啊，皆音希望即係廖長江議員同埋啊所有議員咧係一齊工作。我哋嘅目標都係啊早一日。
我諗誒，當議員知道有一個咁重要嘅法案首讀二讀咧，大家頭先我覺得咧，依一個都係我哋嘅第七屆立法會嘅光明。咁大家係盡一切時間誒去做。我知道有啲議員係已經來往咗誒北京兩次啊，有啲喺外地誒做緊。